Guide to the Cornell University Council records, 1951-2008,
Cornell University Council records
- 8-2-1359, Public Information Office records regarding the Council
  - Special Events, 1962-1963: Cornell University Council. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Accounts
    - Council - Weekend Expenses (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 46)
    - Council - 15th Annual Meeting (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 47)
    - Council - 16th Annual Meeting (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 48)
    - Council - 14th Annual Meeting (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 49)
    - Misc. Conference Papers, 1961-1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 50)
    - Misc. Conference Papers, 1960-1961 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 51)
    - Misc. Papers, 1960 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 52)
    - Special Events - Lynn's File (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 1)
    - Arthur Dean Testimonial Dinner, January 24, 1963 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 2)
    - Lavoisier Collection Dinner, April 19, 1963 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 3)
    - Lafayette Collection Dinner, April 17, 1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 4)
    - Malott Hall - Photographs and Texts (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 5)
    - Institution for Organization Management, 1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 6)
    - Hughes Hall Dedication, December 4, 1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 7)
    - Malott Hall Dedication, October 8, 1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 8)
    - Master Calender - University - CLAY, 1965-1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 9)
    - Scout Career Day, May 22, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 10)
    - Professors-At-Large Dinner, April 30, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 11)
    - Sartre Messenger Lectures, April 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 12)
    - Math Conference, August 30 - September 3, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 13)
    - Clark Hall Dedication, October 20, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 14)
    - Dedications - Physical Sciences Building (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 15)
    - Clark Hall - Guest Lists (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 16)
    - Clark Hall Publications (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 17)
    - Clark Hall Dedication, October 20, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 18)
    - Clark Hall Dedication, October 20, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 19)
    - John R. Mott Centennial, December 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 20)
    - Dante Celebration, November 1-3, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 21)
    - Bioclimatic Labs Dedication, October 26, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 22)
    - Clark Hall Room Reservations (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 23)
    - State Planning Conference, March 22-24, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 24)
    - Morrill Hall, September 12, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 25)
    - Dedication - Langmuir Laboratory, May 27, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 26)
    - Engineering Physics and Aerospace - 20th Anniversary, June 16-17, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 27)
    - CLAY Alumni Seminar, June 15-18, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 28)
    - Trustee Dinner - Clark Hall - John Marcham, June 12, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 29)
    - Democratic Forum, May 14, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 30)
    - Water Resources Lunch and Tour, May 11, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Leader Weekend, May 6-8, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 32)
    - C.U. Council Administrative Meeting, April 15-16, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 2, Folder 33)
  - Cornell University Council - Annual Meetings, 1951 - 1967. Bound folders containing invitations, reservation forms, attendance lists, program of events, menus, and a game program
    - Seventeenth Annual Meeting, October 19-21, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 1)
      Contains Space Sciences Building Dedication, Harvard-Cornell game program
    - Sixteenth Annual Meeting, October 6-8, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 2)
      Contains correspondence, an article on the Council, and the Pennsylvania-Cornell game program
    - Fifteenth Annual Meeting, October 7-9, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 3)
      Contains "A Tour of Clark Hall of Science," "Cornell Latin American Year" booklet, Princeton-Cornell game program
    - Fourteenth Annual Meeting, October 8-10, 1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 4)
      Contains Malott Hall booklet, Centennial booklets and article, Pennsylvania-Cornell game program
    - Thirteenth Annual Meeting, October 4-5, 1963 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 5)
      Contains James Alfred Perkins Inauguration Luncheon and Address program, article on Perkins's installation, article on marijuana on campus
    - Twelfth Annual Meeting, October 5-6, 1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 6)
      Contains "The Role of the University in Promoting Change," Cornell Daily Sun Centennial Edition, Harvard-Cornell Game Program
    - Eleventh Annual Meeting, October 13-14, 1961 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 7)
      Contains "The Growth of Knowledge: The New Threat to Education?," Nuclear reactor article, Navy-Cornell Game Program
    - Tenth Annual Meeting, October 7-8, 1960 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 8)
      Cornell University Announcements: College of Architecture, City and Regional Planning Pamphlet, misc. articles, Cornell-Harvard Game Program
    - Ninth Annual Meeting, October 16-17, 1959 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 9)
      "The Educational Pace is Getting Faster" Speech transcript, "Hollister Hall - College of Engineering" Pamphlet, Cornell Alumni News, photographs, Yale-Cornell Game Program
    - Eighth Annual Meeting, October 3-4, 1958 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 10)
      "The Story of Cornell University" pamphlet, misc. articles, "Letter from Cornell," photographs, Alumni Newsletter
    - Seventh Annual Meeting, October 11-12, 1957 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 11)
      "Greatest Schools in Nation" Chicago Tribute Survey, Syracuse-Cornell Game Program
    - Sixth Annual Meeting, October 5-6, 1956 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 12)
      Council reporter, "For Ezra Cornell - A 150th Birthday Anniversary Dinner,"
    - Fifth Annual Meeting, September 30 - October 1, 1955 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 13)
      Photographs
    - Fourth Annual Meeting, October 1-2, 1954 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 14)
      Annual Meeting Attendance Spreadsheet, Press Release, "What Size Cornell?" address, "From Now to 1960 - A Preview," photographs
    - Third Annual Meeting, October 2-3, 1953 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 15)
      "A Look Down the Future Years" address, photographs
    - Second Annual Meeting, October 4, 1952 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 16)
      Misc. articles
    - First Annual Meeting, October 12, 1951 (Box 8-2-1359 - 3, Folder 17)
      Map of Ithaca, press release, misc. articles,
  - Other Council Papers
    - Centennial Celebration, 1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 1)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 2)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1963 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 3)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 4)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1961 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 5)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1960 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 6)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1959 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 7)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1958 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 8)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1957 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 9)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1955-1956 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 10)
    - Materials Sent to Council Members, 1951-1954 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 11)
    - 11th Annual Meeting Materials, 1961 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 12)
    - Council Meeting Papers, 1957-1960 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 13)
    - Council Roster, 1952-1953 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 14)
    - Council Roster, 1951-1952 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 15)
    - Council Mailings, 1965-1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 16)
    - Cornell University Speakers Bureau - Negatives from G.P. Coleman (Box 8-2-1359 - 4, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Rosters - 1953-1968, Administrative Board Minutes - 1950-1966. Bound folders
    - Administrative Board, 1950-1952 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Board, 1953-1955 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Board and Executive Committee Minutes, 1956 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Board, 1956 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Board, 1957 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Board, 1958 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Board, 1959 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Board, 1960 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Board, 1961 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Board, 1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 10)
    - Administrative Board, 1963-1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Board, 1964-1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 12)
    - Administrative Board, 1965-1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 13)
    - Council Roster, 1953-1954 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 14)
    - Council Roster, 1954-1955 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 15)
    - Council Roster, 1955-1956 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 16)
    - Council Manual, 1956-1957 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 17)
    - Council Manual, 1957-1958 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 18)
    - Council Manual, 1958-1959 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 19)
    - Council Manual, 1959-1960 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 20)
    - Council Manual, 1960-1961 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 21)
    - Council Manual, 1961-1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 22)
    - Council Manual, 1962-1963 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 23)
    - Council Manual, 1963-1964 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 24)
    - Council Manual, 1964-1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 25)
    - Council Manual, 1965-1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 26)
    - Council Manual, 1966-1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 5, Folder 27)
  - Special Events
    - Misc. Papers (Bound), 1966-1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry Research Building Dedication, May 4, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 2 A-C)
    - Noyes Student Center Dedication, October 13, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 3)
    - Population Seminar, November 17-19, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 4)
    - Gev. Synchrotron Dedication, October 10, 1968 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Norman Moore Testimonial, April 14, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 6)
    - Edna McConnell Clark Library (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 7)
    - Trethaway Visitors (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 8)
    - Hans Bethe Dinner, November 16, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 9)
    - Agronomy Dedication, December 5, 1968 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 10)
    - Dean - Cisler Dinner, December 4, 1968 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 11)
    - Space Sciences Building Dedication, October 19, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 12)
    - Kaufmann Auditorium Dedication, October 21, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 13)
    - Cornell Fund Meeting, October 1, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 14)
    - Art Museum Associates, April 8-9, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 15)
    - Regional Conference on the International Educational Act, August 7, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 16)
    - Scout Day, October 1, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 17)
    - Regional Theatre Conference, April 14-16, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 18)
    - Harry Caplan Dinner, May 15, 1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 19)
    - Cornell Conference for Science Writers, May 15-16, 1968 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 20)
    - Room Reservations (Guest and Lecture) (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 21)
    - News Releases (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 22)
    - Leavis (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 23)
    - Von Wright (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 24)
    - Society for Humanities (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 25)
    - Biographical Memoir of Elmer Ambrose Sperry, 1955 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 26)
    - Sperry Hall Dedication, November 1, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 27)
    - Drug Day, September 27, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 28)
    - Hans Bethe Testimonial Dinner, October 21, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 29)
    - Class of 1926 Hall Dedication, October 22, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 30)
    - Society for Humanities Guest Lists, Invitations, 1966-1967 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 31)
    - Society for Humanities Inauguration, October 27, 1966 (Box 8-2-1359 - 6, Folder 32)